MUHAMMAD WASEEM SABIR

MOTION DESIGNER / EDITOR



Phone: +92 3126448488 **Area:** New Garden Town.

Lahore

Email: waseemkathia@gmail.com

Portfolio: https://bit.ly/48g6lct

EXPERIENCE

MOTION DESIGNER

PetaStorm

- 2022- 2023
- Create motion graphics for e-learning
- Create animated explainer videos.
- Review videos for post production and give feedback.

MOTION DESIGNER

Educative

2021- 2022

- Prepared design plans, concept and layout for motion graphic projects.
- Created animations and video content for digital advertisements and social media.
- Edited Educative Sessions podcast.
- Captured videos of in-house activities, events, and talks.
- Created video explainers for YouTube.
- -Managed motion design team.

MOTION DESIGNER /EDITOR

ExamBites

2016- 2021

- Implemented motion graphics for the e-learning using Adobe After Effects, Premiere Pro.
- Designed storyboards and made 2D animations.
- Modeled 3D assets for e-learning animations.

GRAPHICS & WEB DESIGNER

Haddocksoft

2015- 2016

- Designed social media campaigns for more than 20 brands.
- Implemented websites, mobile applications, and landing pages from concept through deployment.
- Assessed UX and UI designs for technical feasibility.

VOLUNTEER WORK _____

MENTOR

The Citizen Foundation

2019-PRE

- -Mentoring the youth to become responsible and productive members of the society.
- -Teaching kids "Thought to Destiny' outlook which serves as the guiding principle to inspire young minds.

EDUCATION

PGD

Virtual University of Pakistan

2021-2022

Post Graduate Diploma in Business administration

MCS

COMSATS INSTITUE OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY,

2013-2015

SAHIWAL CAMPUS
Master of Computer Science (MCS)

ABOUT ME

Experienced Motion Designer with a demonstrated history of working in the e-learning industry and digital advertisement. Skilled in 2D animations and motion graphics. Strong arts and design professional with a Master Degree focused in Computer Science from COMSATS Institute of Information and Technology.

Certifications _____

The Fundamentals of Digital Marketing

by Google Digital Garage

SKILLS ____



Creativity

Tools















